<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://kpango.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kpango.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/angelhack-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/angelhack-2016/</guid>
      <description>Our team has developed an automatic photo organization application. It is an application that makes it easier to see the album by analyzing the images of the photos, classifying them appropriately, and saving them in the collection. Regarding core functions, we perform machine learning using NGT and vector search and achieve a similar comparison using API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/hackday-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/hackday-2019/</guid>
      <description>Our team has developed an application that allows users to try on kimonos without having to wear them by detecting the skeleton by the deep-learning of a person and the skeleton of the kimono&amp;rsquo;s image and synthesizing the images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/hacku-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/hacku-2014/</guid>
      <description>I participated in Hackathon for students sponsored by Yahoo Japan and received a technology prize. Our team has developed an SNS using a two-way crossing mesh network called Ripple. It uses Android and Bluetooth technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/ipsj-iaa-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/ipsj-iaa-2019/</guid>
      <description>Development of Open-source Nearest Neighbor Search that Achieved World Top-level Performance for High-dimensional Vectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/pwc-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/pwc-2017/</guid>
      <description>Our team has developed a sharing time SNS called &amp;ldquo;SMILE MILE&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;SMILE MILE&amp;rdquo; is an application that can find people who act with me at events such as Tokyo 2020. Finally, when two people take pictures, we can analyze facial images by machine learning &amp;amp; evaluate &amp;ldquo;degree of smiling&amp;rdquo;, and users can stock &amp;ldquo;smile miles&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/sbcloud-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/sbcloud-2016/</guid>
      <description>Our team has developed an online medical passport called &amp;ldquo;MediPass&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;MediPass&amp;rdquo; is an Android application that allows you to save your personal medical history online. It is convenient because you can share your medical history across countries when traveling or living abroad. We won the Championship Award and got great feedback from Eric Gun. I learned how to make business solutions in the medical field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/nojima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/nojima/</guid>
      <description>As an intern, I gained experience in the development of EC site backend systems, in-house Q&amp;amp;A systems, and PoS systems. Furthermore, I also got the opportunity to be the internship team leader for the Q&amp;amp;A system and learned to lead a team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/softbank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/softbank/</guid>
      <description>I was in charge of the deployment design and network construction design of the multi-service access node nationwide on the access node team. I developed the deployment prediction software creating my feedback algorithm. This algorithm can predict the number of servers so that the equipment of the ring network and construction can be adjusted accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-go/</guid>
      <description>The Go language technical support team develops internal Go language libraries, creates model cases, maintains CI / CD for Go, and so on.
I regularly lead study sessions to teach the other engineers about the Go language. In these workshops, all attendees from beginners to intermediates can focus on learning Go or getting better at it. At the largest study meeting, more than 200 in-house engineers attended, including myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-hr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-hr/</guid>
      <description>In addition to SWAT, I also worked in the HR Strategy department.
I was an advisor to the Human Resources Department. As an incumbent engineer, I worked on analyzing the hiring demand of Yahoo Japan engineers by job type from two perspectives, technology and field perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-swat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-swat/</guid>
      <description>SWAT is a task force team gathering the most skillful internal engineers. SWAT participates in various projects inside the company to resolve different internal technical problems.
The details of the key projects are mentioned below.
  In-house Centralized Customer Services Platform
Architectural Adviser	2019/6~2019/8
I supported the new In-house centralized customer service platform team as an architectural adviser, and we already have over 200 CS tools in our company. It was not possible for us to improve CS quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-techlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-techlab/</guid>
      <description>Technology Incubation is the R&amp;amp;D department. We work closely with our services and provide new technology to services.
Currently, we work on video analysis &amp;amp; advertisement optimization by image analysis &amp;amp; shopping item recommendation by using image feature vector analysis.
  Product Owner of Technology Area	2020/4~present
Responsible for managing the Technology Incubation team&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology areas. Mainly manages three products, vector search technology (Vald), anomaly detection for infrastructure, and in-house NewSQL areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/athenz-authorizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/athenz-authorizer/</guid>
      <description>Athenz authorizer is a library for Go that manages the policies and certificate of Athenz, and provides authentication and authorization check logic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/athenz-client-sidecar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/athenz-client-sidecar/</guid>
      <description>Athenz client sidecar is an implementation of Kubernetes&amp;rsquo;s sidecar container and provides a common interface to retrieve authentication and authorization credentials from the Athenz server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/authorization-proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/authorization-proxy/</guid>
      <description>Authorization-Proxy is Kubernetes&amp;rsquo;s sidecar container ant provides a common authentication and authorization interface for the user. which enables authentication and authorization checks for specific URL resources.
It fetches the policies from yahoo&amp;rsquo;s Athenz. Then it provides a reverse proxy interface for the user to authenticate the role token written on the request header, in order to allow or reject the user&amp;rsquo;s specific URL request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/gache/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/gache/</guid>
      <description>gache is an ultra-fast lock-free cache library using a concurrent map &amp;amp; xxhash algorithm.
Gache is used in many of Yahoo Japan&amp;rsquo;s Go language platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/garm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/garm/</guid>
      <description>Garm is an API for a Kubernetes authorization webhook that integrates with Athenz for access checks. It allows flexible resource mapping from Kubernetes resources to Athenz ones.
Yahoo Japan uses Garm and Kubernetes AccessReview Webhook to integrate and manage hundreds of large Kubernetes clusters based on the concept of SSoT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/gimbal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/gimbal/</guid>
      <description>Heptio Gimbal is an ingress load-balancing platform capable of routing traffic to multiple Kubernetes and OpenStack clusters. Built by Heptio in partnership with Actapio &amp;amp; Yahoo Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/glg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/glg/</guid>
      <description>glg is faster than Go standard logger and provides leveled logging and colorized output option.
Glg is used by many of Yahoo Japan&amp;rsquo;s Go language platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/gongt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/gongt/</guid>
      <description>Gongt is Go SDK for ngt core</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/ngtd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/ngtd/</guid>
      <description>NGTD is a VectorDatabase that provides approximately neighborhood search of dense vectors via REST / gRPC. was used as a core function of similar image search and recommendation engine of Yahoo Japan. now, NGTD will be replaced with Vald.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/projects/vald/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/projects/vald/</guid>
      <description>Vald is a highly scalable distributed high-speed approximate nearest neighbor dense vector search engine.
Yahoo! JAPAN uses vald for their similar image search engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/summary/</guid>
      <description>I have numerous responsibilities regarding the development and system architecture using a wide range of technologies at Yahoo Japan&amp;rsquo;s Technology Incubation.
My biggest strength is that I&amp;rsquo;m a fast learner and can easily use new technology. Even if I get assigned to a new project and have to use unfamiliar technology, I can take over the leadership of this project in less than one week.
I&amp;rsquo;m exceptionally proficient in Go, and in addition to possessing abundant experience with different programming languages, I also have a profound knowledge starting from infrastructures such as Kubernetes, OpenStack, to vector search engines like Vald.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
