<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Awards on </title>
    <link>https://kpango.com/awards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Awards on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kpango.com/awards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/angelhack-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/angelhack-2016/</guid>
      <description>Our team has developed an automatic photo organization application. It is an application that makes it easier to see the album by analyzing the images of the photos, classifying them appropriately, and saving them in the collection. Regarding core functions, we perform machine learning using NGT and vector search and achieve a similar comparison using API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/hacku-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/hacku-2014/</guid>
      <description>I participated in Hackathon for students sponsored by Yahoo Japan and received a technology prize. Our team has developed an SNS using a two-way crossing mesh network called Ripple it uses Android and Bluetooth technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/ipsj-iaa-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/ipsj-iaa-2019/</guid>
      <description>Development of Open-source Nearest Neighbor Search that Achieved World Top-level Performance for High-dimensional Vectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/pwc-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/pwc-2017/</guid>
      <description>Our team has developed a sharing time SNS called &amp;ldquo;SMILE MILE&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;SMILE MILE&amp;rdquo; is an application that can find people who act with me at events such as Tokyo 2020. Finally, when two people take pictures, we can analyze facial images by machine learning &amp;amp; evaluate &amp;ldquo;degree of smiling&amp;rdquo;, and users can stock &amp;ldquo;smile miles&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/awards/sbcloud-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/awards/sbcloud-2016/</guid>
      <description>Our team has developed an online medical passport called &amp;ldquo;MediPass&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;MediPass&amp;rdquo; is an Android application that allows you to save your personal medical history online. It is convenient because you can share your medical history across countries when traveling or living abroad. We won the Championship Award and got great feedback from Eric Gun. I learned how to make business solutions in the medical field.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>