<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experiences on </title>
    <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experiences on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kpango.com/experiences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/nojima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/nojima/</guid>
      <description>As an internship, I gained experience in the development of EC site backend systems, in-house Q&amp;amp;A systems and PoS systems. Furthermore, I also got the opportunity to be the internship team leader for the Q&amp;amp;A system and learnt to lead a team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/softbank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/softbank/</guid>
      <description>I was in charge of the deployment design and network construction design of the multi-service access node nationwide on the access node team. I developed the deployment prediction software creating my feedback algorithm. This algorithm can predict the number of servers so that the equipment of the ring network and construction can be adjusted accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-go/</guid>
      <description>The Go language technical support team develops internal Go language libraries creates model cases, maintains CI / CD for Go, and so on.
I regularly lead study sessions to teach the other engineers about the Go language. In these workshops, all attendees from beginners to intermediates can focus on learning golang or getting better at it. To the largest study meeting came more than 200 in-house engineers, including me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-hr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-hr/</guid>
      <description>In addition to SWAT, I also worked in the HR strategy work department.
I was in charge of an advisor to the Human Resources Department. As an incumbent engineer, I worked on analysing the hiring demand of Yahoo Japan engineers by job type from two perspectives, technology and field perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-swat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-swat/</guid>
      <description>SWAT is a task force team gathering the most skilful internal engineers. SWAT participates in various projects inside the company to resolve different internal technical problems.
The details of the key projects mentioned below.
  In-house Centralized Customer Services Platform
Architectural Adviser	2019/6~2019/8
I supported the new In-house centralised customer service platform team as an architectural adviser, and we already have over 200 CS tools in our company. We can not improve CS quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-techlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kpango.com/experiences/yahoo-techlab/</guid>
      <description>Tech Lab is the R&amp;amp;D department. We work closely with our services and provide new technology to services.
Currently, we work on video analysis &amp;amp; advertisement optimization by image analysis &amp;amp; shopping item recommendation by using image feature vector analysis.
 Next Generation Vector Search Engine Platform
Founder &amp;amp; Lead Developer (Go/C++/Python/Kubernetes/OpenStack)	2019/8~present
I&amp;rsquo;m working on the development of distributed approximation KNN graph and tree dense-vector search engine for large-scale vector data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>